<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="ga_trackingId">UA-44536689-1</string>
    <string name="app_name">Network Connections</string>
    <string name="legaltxt">"GOOGLE MAPS API. Maps data is provided by Google. By using Network Connections app, you agree to be bound by the Google Maps Terms of Service (http://www.google.com/help/terms_maps.html). 

Network Information data is provided for your personal use and on your behalf from ARIN (American Registry for Internet Numbers), RIPE (Réseaux IP Européens) and APNIC (Asia Pacific Network Information Centre). Therefore using this software you agree with the terms provided by the aforementioned authorities: https://www.arin.net/whois_tou.html, https://www.ripe.net/data-tools/support/documentation/terms and https://www.apnic.net/services/manage-resources/digital-certificates/terms-and-conditions 

ABUSE RBL DATA IS PROVIDED BY UCEPROTECT-Network. THE DATA IS PROVIDED 'AS IS' AND THE AUTHOR DISCLAIMS ALL WARRANTIES WITH REGARD TO THIS DATA INCLUDING ALL IMPLIED WARRANTIES OF MERCHANTABILITY AND FITNESS. IN NO EVENT SHALL THE AUTHOR BE LIABLE FOR ANY SPECIAL, DIRECT, INDIRECT, OR CONSEQUENTIAL DAMAGES OR ANY DAMAGES WHATSOEVER RESULTING FROM LOSS OF USE, DATA OR PROFITS, WHETHER IN AN ACTION OF CONTRACT, NEGLIGENCE OR OTHER TORTIOUS ACTION, ARISING OUT OF OR IN CONNECTION WITH THE USE OR PERFORMANCE OF THIS DATA. 

DISCLAIMER OF WARRANTY ON SOFTWARE: YOU EXPRESSLY UNDERSTAND AND AGREE THAT YOUR USE OF THE APPLICATION IS AT YOUR SOLE RISK AND THAT THE APPLICATION IS PROVIDED AS IS AND AS AVAILABLE WITHOUT WARRANTY OF ANY KIND. YOU ARE SOLELY RESPONSIBLE FOR ANY DAMAGE TO YOUR DEVICE OR LOSS OF DATA THAT RESULTS FROM SUCH USE. PROFESSIONAL AMERICAN SYSTEM SERVICE CORP, ITS LICENSORS AND DISTRIBUTORS DO NOT GUARANTEE THIS APPLICATION IN TERMS OF THEIR ACCURACY, RELIABILITY, OR OTHERWISE. PROFESSIONAL AMERICAN SYSTEM SERVICE CORP AND ITS LICENSORS AND DISTRIBUTORS EXPRESSLY DISCLAIM ALL IMPLIED WARRANTIES, INCLUDING BUT NOT LIMITED TO IMPLIED WARRANTIES OF TITLE, AVAILABILITY, PERFORMANCE, NON-INFRINGEMENT, MERCHANTABILITY OR FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE. YOU ASSUME THE ENTIRE RISK AS TO THE RESULTS AND PERFORMANCE OF THE APPLICATION, INFORMATION PRESENTED IN IT AND RELATED DOCUMENTATION. THE APP MAY ANONYMOUSLY TRACK AND REPORT USERS'S ACTIVITY (WITH GOOGLE ANALYTICS CODE) INSIDE THE APP IN ORDER TO PROVIDE BETTER INTERFACE AND STABILITY."</string>
    <string name="welcome">"Welcome to

"</string>
    <string name="legal">"By tapping on 'Continue' you agree to the"</string>
    <string name="termsOfService">Terms of Service</string>
</resources>
